Hello, I'm Hiker CP, and I'm here
at the familiar forest road.
This time we'll take the familiar
and unfamiliar route.
This is Gandhiwan.
There's a special significance
for me,
and that's to finish it in 2022.
I rested for a while in the
Central Mountain Range,
and then I left in April.
Then in May,
June, July, I'll go up the
mountain to Chokwan Peak.
Back then, it was kind
of a crappy climb.
It's weird that I'm here on vacation,
but today I'm here to fuck Chovan.
There is no route
on the map.
So he's been doing a little
bit of exploring,
and then the record is very,
very short.
It's great to see that you're
not alone anymore,
because you've seen a
lot of your buddies.
In fact, I only knew one person before I went public,
and I didn't
know any of the others,
and I didn't tell anyone about them.
I've climbed mountains,
and the amazing thing is,
I'm the only one who's ever been to Gandjom.
No one else has been here before! Let's
see if this trip is worth it.
I'd like to share with you
what happens when friends
who've climbed mountains
climb together.
We were kind of hoping that nothing
would happen without it.
The most important thing in any story
is to get off the mountain safely,
but since we're all
experienced hikers.
We're not novices,
we just haven't climbed together.
9.1K from the trailhead should
be the end of the line.
I've been away for too long,
and actually, I'm sorry.
I'm excited because this was supposed to be a four
-day trip,
so look at my back.
He's got an oversized backpack,
and he's carrying a
It's the first time in years that I've
climbed a mountain in disguise,
and "disguise" isn't disguise.
I've been thinking about changing
to a shorter lens,
but I've been thinking about changing to a shorter lens,
but I've been thinking about changing to a shorter lens.
We don't have any money lately,
so we're just going to put the original
I brought the lens with me,
but it's okay, it's about 1K 1kg (A7Cll + 28
-75mm), so I don't have any lenses.
The whole bag weighs about 13 kilograms.
It's heavy to carry,
but it's heavy to carry on my back.
It's not bad at all,
but this Bonfus backpack is really
powerful! Because of this.
I can carry up to 18kg,
so this 13kg is a small case. A backpack is a small case,
but a person is not a small case. ......
You're still a little out of breath
when you're really walking.
Today we're expected
to walk to Mushanchi,
and they said it's impossible to get there,
so I told them.
I'll be fine. Last time I snored,
it was the last time I snored.
I'm going up like this.
I'm going up first because I'm out of breath.
Dogs, if you come the day
before you can advance.
Come to sleep in the workhouse
(tin) Overgrown with weeds
（How can there be kiwi
fruit in the mountains?
QQ, good luck!
QQ, go to hell!
Steeple, here's my bag
of pills, just in case.
It's too early to eat.
Have we been walking for an hour?
It's a green kiwi,
not a golden kiwi (how on earth
could there be one in Lindau?).
(The water is huge.) (There
are some side slopes,
similar to the North 2 section.)
(AKIWEI Nightcrawler,
purple and cool!)
It's raining in a typhoon,
so I think it's better than the road.
Three years ago, it was a lot harder to walk,
and then the strips were gone.
The road is all crooked,
so I don't think it's that easy,
so don't go without a guide.
Come on, let's go. He'll hate you forever.
He'll never be with you.
There's water all
along the trail.
Bring me a fried chicken
for dinner. Okay,
I'll spray it right away.
The lens cap's gone.
Sprayed MDFK !!!!! again.
（It's really hard to get around.
The ridges are slower.
It's not what I remember about Godzilla.
We're going to have to do it now.
I'm left with Deke and I'm
waiting for the 3000M
to come out of the meadow
and then we'll go.
We'll go up to Gandhiwan,
new shoes, Mount to Coast,
and walk for three days.
2972M, distant Kandrawan,
right over, waist over.
Eat jerky with Korean
nuts! Milk type east,
black water
If you don't want to drink the black water,
come from Ten Grains Creek.
Or this side of the water?
You're going to
fish for water? Do you
have enough water?
(Is this the last one?) No,
I'm just looking at Tianchi.
It's okay. The sun's
shining. The ridge
is coming up.
We're going to Gandjovan.
Josha, the 18 peaks are scary.
Wushe Reservoir.
We have to go a little further,
a little further out of this meadow,
it's been a long time since I've been here.
Dry Jovan is a very tired man.
Behind me is Kandrawan,
and over here.
Josha, the 18th peak (on the right).
Where's the road to Chovan?
I think it's a mess,
and then there's no fabric.
Typhoon day ah messy road
like this a little long,
did not carry heavy objects 14kg
It's been a long time since I've
carried a kilo like this.
We'll carry less than 10 kilos,
and hopefully we'll make it to Sancha
and Mushanchi before nightfall.
The water is not very hot,
maybe the temperature is comfortable,
about 25 degrees, but it's not very hot.
Sometimes it's very sunny,
but mostly in the forest,
it's okay with this fantastic wool blend.
It's very quick
-drying. It's cool. I don't know why.
The inexplicable feeling
of a cool ice jacket (???
A more expensive ice jacket
XDDD Don’t make a noise,
you beast! !
Why is there no brand?
The brand is gone.
The brand is gone. There is no brand.
Second look!! Who took
the sign away??
Was it blown away by the wind?
(Found it XD) It's too cold
to walk around in the sun
(After getting off Zhuo Wan,
you have to walk a lot)
(Lots of rope climbing terrain) (When
you are in a hurry and hungry,
FAST pectin is the best choice)
Wear the GORE
-TEX mid-layer and put it inside the bag,
so you only wear the outer shell
Climb up and you will almost reach
the Three Forks Campground
The first one is a male
with a mother and child
behind him! (First time
seeing a family photo!!)
This is a strange
black pond.
It's OK.
It takes about 10 hours and
15 minutes to get to Sancha.
Suddenly I felt like
I had walked so far,
from 7 people to 2 people.
It's hard for large
groups to get here.
I miscalculated because I had
to arrive 2 hours earlier.
We were supposed to leave at 6 o'clock,
but we left at 8 o'clock, so it's 5 o'clock now.
If you leave at 6 o'clock,
it will be 15:00 when you get back,
which is pretty good.
We arrived at Sancha,
but the wind was too strong to camp.
Find a place,
it's cold enough to climb 2000M+17K. Okay,
we are going to find it here now.
The wind is too strong
here in the cave camp
Find a relatively low place.
The wind is sometimes there and sometimes not.
There is a Kantian Pond next to it,
so I didn't go to the Mushan Pond to get water.
I hope there will be no more wind at night.
First, set up your own tent!
OCTA material warm mid
-layer
(Kawas Lightest Down
Jacket) (Lanerhead
Ultra
-Light Waterproof GORE-TEX Jacket)
Pressure cooker (??? The wind
is super strong and the fire
is burning XD I will eat a pack
of rice for dinner today
Then eat noodles,
noodles with dried meat and crispy cod fish
Rice can also be added
with dried vegetables
and soaked in a cup of soup.
Soak the vegetables,
meat, and instant noodles in cold water first and then cook
them after the noodles are soaked (it will cook faster).
(Remember not to get too close to
the tent when the wind is strong)
zpacks (My old model tent rope is this thick,
the new model (2024)
zpacks are so thin and the
fabric is getting thinner!
Cutting corners (? And then
selling it at a higher price
(The wind continued to blow at night.
..) (I thought it was a typhoon.
..) (＊＆＾％＄)
I'm having a headache
from the breakdown.
I hope I don't have a headache when I wake up tomorrow. If I have a headache,
I don't have to leave.
Today is much more tiring
than expected.
I am busy with Zhuo Wan.
It is far and difficult to walk.
The road is rotten.
There are very few strips of cloth.
I wonder if they have been removed.
After four collaborations,
I’m still trying to find my way XDDD
Hahahaha, I am so frustrated today.
I am going up steeply
with heavy equipment.
The wind is still so strong,
I use my weight to calm it down.
But it's not extremely
cold because it's
summer and the wind in summer
is not that cold.
It's still a bit cold
and can't blow.
There are about five
sambar deer outside.
5, not giraffes, but sambar deer.
They are all females.
I have confirmed that it is useless (??
Haha I don't want to pee on them either! No,
I'll wait.
I'll go pee (a fickle man)
Tomorrow will be the same
Go up the steep East
Peak and then cut
down to the west to Twin Mountains.
It will be easier today.
I found that the third day is really tiring.
We have to start from
The volcano kicked out the
trailhead very far...
It's a downhill slope,
but the way up is hard to find,
and the way down is also steep.
It's not very good, so I hope to
Relax and camp near the volcano
You can go down the mountain
early the day after tomorrow.
See you tomorrow.
Bye bye
hello
Hey (give me
some alms!)
Oh~~~So cool~~So cool~!!
Oh~~~so good~~so good~!!
Enjoy eating,
enjoy eating! ! Hi,
Xipi's urine tastes so good! ! ～～
Hey, eat quickly (my face is already
sunken after just one day...)
(Humans are so noisy)
The good thing is that
there is really no shortage of water.
Up to Ganzhuowan